

Anil Berdan Ceylan

I started my university life as an Electrical and Electronics
Engineering student, and as a result of analyzing my skills and interests more accurately, I go on my way as a Computer Engineering student. My aim is to take firm steps in my career with the experiences I have gained and to take part in meaningful works.

Ankara - Turkey

+90 536 953 1896

☑ anil.ceylan@metu.edu.tr

www.linkedin.com/in/anil-berdanceylan
github.com/ABCeylan

Portfolio
abceylan.github.io

Languages

- o Turkish (Native)
- English (Advanced)
- German (Elementary)

Hobbies / Interests

- Sailing
- Scuba Diving
- Skiing
- Cooking
- Travelling
- Video Games
- o AR-VR

Education

2017-2023(Expected) METU - Computer Engineering

Related Coursework: Data Structures, Algorithms, Database Management Systems & File Structures, Computer Organization.

2013-2017 Rasim Sahinkaya Science High School

Experience

Dec. 2021 – Current Game Development Tutor

HUB21 - REMOTE

I give lessons of Scratch, Construct3 and Unity to children aged 13 to 17.

Nov. 2021 – March 2022 Monster Gaming Lab Project Member

MONSTER - REMOTE

We created a full 2D comic type platformer game using Unity with my team.

Aug. 2021 – Oct. 2021 Software Developer Intern

BUYUTECH TECH COMPANY - ANKARA

My aim was writing drivers for different kinds of camera sensors for various purposes.

Club & Association Memberships

2021-Current Google Developer Students Club - METU Game Dev. (Member)

2019-Current METU Sailing Team (Member)

2018-Current ACM Student Chapter - METU (Member)

Skills

- C / C# / C++
- Unity
- Java
- MySQL
- Python
- Assembly
- Verilog